betpractice.com 2014-05-17

# Betpractice's privacy policy

Betpractice is committed to preserving the privacy of all visitors to our website at http://www.betpractice.com. Please read the following privacy policy to understand how we use and protect the information that you provide to us. By registering or placing an order on this website, you consent to the collection, use and transfer of your information under the terms of this policy.

**1 INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT FROM YOU**  
1.1 When you visit, register or order online services on http://betpractice.com you will be asked to provide certain information about yourself including your email.  
1.2 We may also collect information about your usage of our website as well as information about you from messages you post to the website and e-mails or letters you send to us.  
1.3 We do not collect / or read passwords, credit / debit accounts.

**2 WHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION WE GATHER**  
2.1 It enables us to bill you and to contact you when necessary.  
2.2 We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service.  
2.3 We may use the information to improve our products and services.

**3 LINK TO OTHER WEBSITES - DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION**  
3.1 Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**4 SECURITY AND DATA RETENTION**  
4.1 All your data are encrypted.  
4.2 We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure.  
4.2 Betpractice uses SSL certification for website security service.

**5 CONTROLLING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
5.1 If you have previously agreed, to us for using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may choose to restrict the collection or change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us.  
5.2 We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties, unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.  
5.3 You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to [address].  
5.4 If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

**6   CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**  
6.1 Any changes to our privacy policy in the future will be posted to the website and, where appropriate, through e-mail notification.
